time for tonight's hash
Wars Mark what are you twoo stupid
points Marilyn I'm marrying vodka right
ladies
points Dave no way this lasts gay
points I give it two years yes points
Marilyn sacred Bond my ass Karen
f mark take it from me
[Laughter]
don't Dave oh the bride is super
tight correction the bride was super
tight RN I was super
tight uh Mark you two are great together
I'm not a monster Chris okay no you're
right okay
fine Doug
Benson
want to go to Schindler's party click
here to get on the
list all
right points for that Natasha Dude
Where's My Car the answer may shock you
points Tom Tom Lennon's four weird
tricks to playing a doctor in every
[Applause]
movie you are you might officially be a
position by now points of Tom Lennon
Doug Benson I
don't
Whitney comings 50 Centrum points
Whitney Lauren over the hill FS Chia TP
Shakur Fs in comings Lil John Deer FS
chalia Gucci Mane of the house FS
comings notorious old FS next Fooda
Chris if I have to tell you Ma one more
time God damn
it when comings
lazy